SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
ADAPTED FROM THE EARLY SPRING ON JJWXC.NET
AUTHOR: GU NIANG BIE KU
Let's sit there.
Excuse me.
Forget it.
Sit there.
Those foreigners keep looking at you.
I'm sure they'll chat you up real soon.
Come on.
You dressed so well today.
They're looking at you, not me.
Yes, look at me.
I can practice my English.
After all, we learn a foreign language
to travel the world.
Luke?
I see you made yourself comfortable.
We are doing Lime proud here.
We prove that Lime girls
are not just smart and capable,
but also beautiful.
Of course.
It's all thanks to your guidance.
Right, boss?
Stop it.
No need to flatter me
when we're on vacation.
Buy us a coconut, perhaps?
No.
‪No worries.
It's my treat. I'll buy some.
I'll come with you.
So stingy.
Hey, beauty.
Would you like some coconut juice?
My treat.
DO WE HAVE A FUTURE?
No need.
Thanks.
Lumi. Help me carry it.
What did I just tell you?
They are into you.
Come, boss.
Have a coconut.
No, thanks.
It's a treat from a handsome guy.
It's not right for me to take it.
Who cares? Just enjoy it. Here.
Try it. Here.
No, thanks.
You didn't get his number?
If we're meant to be,
we'll meet again.
Let's not just sit under the sun.
Should we go shopping?
Sure.
Boss, do you want to join us?
No.
Come with us.
- Why?
- To pay.
No girls who wear this
carry money with them.
Come.
Are we seriously spending his money?
Yes.
Now is the best time for him
to show off his generosity.
Splurge.
Eat anything you want.
Don't.
Look at this.
Do you want this one?
Come in.
People will see us if you do this.
Don't wear something like this again.
But I love it.
I want to wear it.
Do you do this to everyone?
Do what?
So controlling.
So possessive.
Others can wear or do whatever they want.
That's their freedom.
But not you.
I don't like it when men look at you.
Am I beautiful?
Yes.
Lethally beautiful.
Wait. Wait.
Someone's calling.
Hello?
Flora. Are you free now?
Yes. Why?
Is something the matter?
Nothing.
There's a bug here.
Go ahead.
Come to the lobby bar.
I want to talk to you.
Okay. I'm coming over now.
- Luan Nian.
- Who's that prick
who talks about work
during a team-building exercise?
Alex.
Why didn't you turn him down?
He's my boss.
I need his vote as well
for my promotion next month.
Before you forget, I can vote too.
I'm sure I can win it by myself.
Let's watch the sunrise
by the beach tomorrow.
Okay.
I have to work now.
Luke.
Can we talk? It's an emergency.
Hello?
Alex is quitting.
- He is quitting?
- Yes.
He just tendered his resignation.
Perhaps you should reflect
on your oversight.
Someone poached our manager,
and you didn't even find out.
I admit it is my fault.
We are conducting an internal review
as we speak.
Don't worry. It won't happen again.
- Again?
- Luke.
Alex quit on us on such short notice.
You are rightfully annoyed.
But our priority now
is to minimize the impact
of Alex's resignation.
Where is he going?
Chuangyu.
An up-and-coming startup.
I can suppress the news for now,
but not for long.
He's leaving at the end of this month.
Okay.
Ask him to tie up the loose ends
of his projects
and hand over everything properly.
In exchange,
I will not hold him accountable
for his infringement.
Make sure to contain the rumors.
I do not want our employees to panic.
Understood. I'll talk to him
after you come back.
Also, pay attention
to Division One and Two.
Alex might poach some people as well.
Who do you think he'll poach?
Why me?
You've worked here
for quite some time, Flora.
I've seen what you can do.
Among the new recruits,
you progress the fastest
and have the biggest potential.
I love your learning speed and resilience.
Are you sure?
Lime has so many capable employees.
Besides,
I'm not even an account manager now.
I have not spearheaded any big projects.
How… How can I be helpful to you?
Why are you doubting yourself?
Are you questioning my judgment now?
- No.
- Come.
Let's go through what you've achieved
in the past two years.
You made Lime's supplier database.
You helped Lime close an important deal
with Yueteng Auto.
And you performed wonderfully
in last month's
automotive exhibition show.
Your resume is stellar.
If it weren't for Luan Nian's meddling,
you would have already become an AM.
Honestly, I feel bad for you.
Join me in Chuangyu.
New company, new stage, new opportunity.
I'll give you the position of AM.
Your salary will be doubled,
and you will lead a team yourself.
No stupid rules to confine you.
You can just shine bright.
Alex, I do not intend
to switch jobs for now.
It's just so sudden.
I… I need time to think it over.
You can get back to me
after you think it through.
But keep this between us.
For our sake, as I'm sure you know.
Yes. Don't worry.
The opportunity waits for no one.
- Cheers!
Thank you, everyone, for joining us.
Other than this trip, your special bonus
will be handed out together
with your salary next month.
Thank you.
- Thank you!
- Thanks, Luke.
Thanks, boss.
Flora.
Alex. Thank you.
Alex.
I have to go now.
You talked to Alex?
Yes.
What did you two talk about?
Just work.
Who do you think he'll poach?
Flora.
Flora?
She was transferred from your team.
I'm surprised she got along
with Alex this well.
Her decision to leave with Alex or not
would be the litmus test of your charisma.
SHANG ZHITAO
I'm here.
Flora,
you've been working at Lime
for several years.
How do you feel?
Aren't we supposed to watch the sunrise?
Why are we talking about work?
I'm grateful for this opportunity
and grateful that your strict guidance
has allowed me to grow rapidly.
Grateful?
Is there nothing else you want to tell me?
No.
Luan Nian.
I'm happy that we get to watch
the sunrise together.
But I hope…
not just the sunrise.
I want to watch the sunset with you too.
Now, I'm done.
The sunrise is so beautiful.
To watch the sunrise with him feels great.
Half of my feelings for him are love.
And the other half
is admiration and respect.
At this moment,
he's standing so close to me.
But this is something
I can't say out loud or hide.
All right.
Let's call it a day.
Compile everything and send it to me
as soon as possible.
- Dismissed.
- I will double check.
- Okay.
- Sorry.
We'll only take up a few minutes.
We have an announcement to make.
Today is my last day at Lime.
I am grateful for your support
and understanding in my journey.
Before the new business manager arrives,
Luke will temporarily
take over Business Division Two.
You have my blessings, Alex.
After I became the general manager,
I am grateful for your support
and the support
from the Customer Service Division.
You have led a formidable team.
I'll leave the floor to all of you.
I reserved a restaurant nearby
for Alex's farewell party.
Join us if you are free.
Thank you, Tracy.
All the best, Alex.
I am honored
to have worked with all of you
all these years.
Don't sulk.
I'm just changing my job.
When you're free, hang out with me.
We can eat or drink.
Let's drink to your heart's content today.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Thanks, Alex.
Thanks, Alex.
See you at the restaurant.
Go back to your work.
- Hi, Alex.
- Alex.
A toast to you.
- A toast to you.
- Together.
Thank you.
May all go well in your next position.
Good luck.
Alex was doing so well.
Why did he leave?
To seek greener pastures.
There's a place better than Lime?
Will you work at Lime forever?
To him, the greener pastures
mean better pay,
bigger space, and more resources.
Then why didn't Lime
give him a counter-offer?
We did.
During the team-building exercise,
Luke talked to him. It didn't go well.
So be it then.
But to Luke,
Lime is never lacking in talent.
I was looking for you.
I know who Alex is taking with him.
Who?
Du Anni and Li Tianran.
Both of them are idiots.
Once they leave Lime,
they'll realize they owe
their stellar achievements
to this company.
Lumi, if it were you, would you leave?
Is this a joke? Why would I leave?
A new place means I have to adapt
to a new environment.
I'm comfortable in Lime.
I've adapted to this place. I own it.
People let me do what I want.
Job-hopping has its pros and cons.
If you leave with him,
you're forever his subordinate.
If he succeeds, you'll be successful.
If he fails, you have to start all over.
But if you stay,
you have to face the new boss.
You don't know if you'll be sidelined.
But as long as you stay in Lime,
Luke will protect you.
Why?
Because Yueteng has retained us.
And you know them very well.
Right?
- Shall we grab a cab?
- My boyfriend is picking my up.
- Bye then.
- Bye.
Flora.
Alex.
You know I want you to come with me.
On top of what I said last time,
there's also a personal reason.
I'll get back to you as soon as possible.
If Alex wants you to go with him,
there can only be two reasons.
You're cheap and obedient.
So even now, that's how he sees me.
If you're leaving,
please tell me beforehand.
I'll talk to HR
and terminate your position.
That way, you can get your severance pay.
Thank you.
Once I have made up my mind,
I'll let you know beforehand.
So you truly are considering
taking up Alex's offer?
He gave you that offer
at Phuket, didn't he?
What did he tell you?
That you would be successful
if you followed him?
That your salary would double
and you would get promoted in a year?
Shang Zhitao, do you have a brain?
Are you trying to fish out
an answer from me?
I wouldn't have to do this
if you didn't lie to me.
I gave you a chance
just now and in Phuket.
But you chose to lie.
Are you that eager to leave with him?
You are not my direct superior.
I would be going over
my superior's head otherwise.
If you want to talk about rules,
according to the company policy,
management-level employees
cannot poach any staff members
as it constitutes unfair competition.
You've signed the non-compete agreement.
Since Alex loves to play dirty,
what do you think
our legal team will do to him?
Shang Zhitao, do you know
what your fundamental problem is?
You do not have a firm principle.
You are young.
How can you let small gains entice you?
Have you thought about your future?
Or are you a shortsighted person
who only sees
the benefits in front of you?
Mr. Luan.
My future?
If I want a future, I need money.
I'm not like you.
You're used to your lofty palace.
That's why you can think
about your future.
I came to Beijing alone
and rented a place with flatmates.
I am cheap and obedient.
It takes three hours
to travel to the office back and forth.
My happiness is decided by cheap things,
like my commute and wage.
Alex told me that the new company
was close to my home.
How can I not be enticed?
Will you even understand my situation?
Can you even empathize?
Besides, this is my private matter.
I don't need your intervention.
You think I want to care about you?
I wouldn't have had to say all this
if you had used your brain once.
Did I beg for your advice?
You want my answer, don't you?
Then, listen carefully.
I'm leaving with Alex. Why?
Because he supports me.
He talks to me nicely.
He respects me.
I wish you all the best.
I will do my best.
Not strong or firm enough.
Cheap. Obedient. Docile.
How can you let small gains entice you?
Have you thought about your future?
Or are you a shortsighted person
who only sees
the benefits in front of you?
Reckless. Didn't think it through. Eager.
LUAN NIAN
IF ALEX WANTS YOU TO GO WITH HIM
THERE CAN ONLY BE TWO REASONS
YOU ARE CHEAP AND OBEDIENT
LUKE
SETTINGS
BLOCK USER
BLOCK
BLOCKED
Why are you following me?
Were you abandoned too?
Dirty fella.
I'll help you find
your owner tomorrow, okay?
Come.
I love the renovation.
Very artsy.
How did you find the designer?
The renovation fee must be…
What's the matter?
Work or girls? Tell me.
Remember Alex?
Shang Zhitao is following Alex
to his new job.
And she lied to me.
I confronted her,
and she said she shouldn't go
over her superior's head.
In my eyes,
Ms. Shang is more rational than you are.
You see.
If people mix work and private life,
there will be no order.
Forget about the relationship.
She is just your subordinate.
She can choose where she wants to work.
So I just watch her
as she makes the wrong decision?
She's just young and reckless.
She gets enticed by the smallest benefit.
A job does not fall into your lap.
You sound like your father.
Easy. Think positively.
If she leaves Lime,
you no longer have to hide
your relationship anymore.
It's a good thing.
Luan Nian.
Ask yourself truthfully.
Are you worried that she'll leave Lime
or that she'll leave you?
Regardless of her choice,
I hope you can respect her.
Because she is an independent person.
If you don't want to lose her,
win her back,
and not just push her away
in a hurtful way.
STUDIO
Spent all 200,000 yuan your mom gave you?
I must say, it's a miracle
that the motley crew of yours
lasted three months.
Why?
Can't take a comment after you failed?
How can you start a business
when you're this sensitive?
Do you think business grows on trees?
How naive.
Starting a business
is not as simple as you think.
The world outside is complicated.
You refused to believe me
and took up a fool's errand.
So for a successful entrepreneur like you,
you only judge people
by how much money they make?
It is not the only standard,
but it's the bare minimum.
Your company didn't make any money.
It was a net loss.
Who are you to judge my standard?
If nothing I do pleases you,
why did you lie that Mom was sick
and ask me to come back?
Why are you two fighting again?
Can't you talk properly?
It's okay.
You don't have to worry about me anymore.
From now on, whether I live or die
has nothing to do with you.
If you use my money, it is my business.
Hush already.
Look at you.
What do you have other than a box?
Enough!
It's not your money.
Luan Nian did the right thing.
I support your decision.
You have my support.
- Let's go back inside.
- Mom.
Two hundred thousand yuan.
I'll repay you together with the interest.
Luan Nian. Luan Nian.
Luan Nian! You…
STUDIO
Are you worried that she'll leave Lime
or that she'll leave you?
If you don't want to lose her,
win her back,
and not just push her away
in a hurtful way.
Shang Zhitao, do you have a brain?
Have you thought about your future?
Or are you a shortsighted person?
I'm leaving with Alex. Why?
Because he supports me.
He talks to me nicely.
He respects me.
Sorry.
The number you called cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
SHANG ZHITAO, WHERE ARE YOU?
THE USER HAS BLOCKED YOUR MESSAGE
Do you think business grows on trees?
How naive.
You took up a fool's errand.
How did I become
the person I hate the most?
It's so solemn in here.
I almost thought
Division Two were getting disbanded.
Report your work to me.
Shang Zhitao.
You're doing the market analytics
for global new media.
How is the progress?
I have collected the necessary data
and will add domestic suppliers
into our media database.
Our rivals are posturing
to enter the new media market.
We have to act quickly now.
How long do you think you need?
A month.
If you can finish it in two weeks,
we'll have the edge.
Can you do it?
Given that we are currently short-staffed,
I am unable to make that promise.
We'll stick to the same goal.
Two weeks.
I'll assign people
from other teams to assist you.
Sit down.
Flora, I can tell you have thought
carefully about your work.
Not only do you work hard,
you have a plan too.
Keep it up.
Flora.
You've changed.
You said no to Luke,
and somehow, he didn't rebut you.
He even praised you.
I was just telling the truth.
Did you tell him you couldn't make it
because you have decided to join Alex?
Let me tell you the truth.
I have not made the decision yet.
I said what I said in the meeting
because it truly is beyond my capability.
Listen.
Personally, I don't want you to leave.
Be it at work or hanging out as friends,
you are an amazing person.
But you decide
if you want to stay or leave.
You are so bright,
you'll shine wherever you go.
You truly think I… I'm very good?
Yes. You're amazing.
Why else did Alex make you that offer?
I will respect your decision.
WORK HARD IN OCTOBER AS WELL!
DAILY ENGLISH STUDY PLAN
CALL THE SUPPLIER
MONTHLY WORK PLAN
I found a job.
Lime!
I got this from Yonghe Palace.
It'll boost your career.
I can't even follow the meeting minutes.
They used so much jargon,
and I don't know them.
I want to master them in a week.
THURSDAY 6 P.M.
STARRY COFFEE SHOP, ENGLISH TUITION
When it comes to language,
speaking especially,
being good at imitating is a perk
because it means you'll learn well.
Spare your gratitude and apologies.
We don't need them at work.
Sir.
I'm Shang Zhitao from Lime Advertising.
We managed to secure
an annual retainer contract
with Mulanshuo.
EXCEL FORMULAS GUIDE
We will categorize suppliers
into three groups.
Each category will be graded
on different criteria.
As the project manager,
I take full responsibility.
I accept any punishment from the company.
Your event was a success.
Everyone in Lime knows your name now.
SUN YU
Sun Yu.
Tao. Something bad happened.
What?
Done.
I'll send them out.
Flora.
- I'm going over there.
- Okay.
MAY YOUR EYES ONLY SEE SMILES
TO: SUN YUANZHU
Are you done?
Done.
You didn't forget anyone?
No. I got them all.
MAY YOU GET PROMOTED SOON. TO: SUN YU
What about me?
You want one too?
What do you think?
I paid for nothing?
Will this work?
WISHING YOU HAPPINESS
I love your handwriting.
I'll take it then.
No need to send it out.
We save the cost of a stamp.
I also get to save the cost of one.
STAY CHEERFUL AND GENUINE FOREVER